Its name is ICC Lombard, an
insurance sector stock. Friends,
you might already know its larger
message, but I want to
focus on the pattern that is forming here. Friends, the pattern that is
visible here is a very good
pattern. Friends,
last Saturday, when we placed
our stop on Infosys, friends, it was placed on this very
pattern. I
told you there that you would buy
Infosys around 1140 or 1147,
and your
target would be 40. I had told you that you would get it between 70 and 75,
between 1170 and 1175.
I will provide you the stock link in my video.
So friends,
I am seeing the same pattern in ICC Lombard.
And look, secondly, this is an insurance
sector stock. ICC itself is a
similar name. Friends, ICC Lombard is the
second stock, friends, you are
getting it around its 52 week low, which is its
52 VIX low, friends, it is around 1049.  It will
happen and right now you are getting the stock
at 1119 i.e. 119,
from there the start is ₹70 above, friends if the stop of 1000 is
found 60-70 above its bottom then it
is good and friends I am
not buying the stock because the
motive of buying is that the pattern that is being formed is a
very good pattern, friends in that pattern
our target for such people will be of 1050 only
i.e. there is a price of 70 points and
friends the target is
1350-1400
plus
how many points can you get from here,
friends if the position is running then it is possible
that you may lose six-seven months time from here
but keep in mind friends
if within one year you people from Nifty i.e.
share market
through swing trading from stock market if you people make
40-50% even 40% 40-50 I have said too much
friends our Rakesh Jhunjhunwala says that
if you people use even 21% then it is a
very good amazing return, so according to that
I  It seems that within 6 months,
this stock will give you a return of around 20%. So, the
technical pattern is quite good. Friends, the
pattern formed in the technical is very
good. I am not going to discuss it too much in the fundamentals.
Tomorrow I will bring you the stock from the technical side
for you friends. Friends, the
rest
come in the Nifty Top 100 stocks. Friends,
ICC Lombard is counted among the Nifty Top 100 stocks. They are available at
excellent rates. Well,
friends, if you want to open your demat account,
if you want to switch from
Kotak Mahindra to Kotak
Securities, then I will provide you its
account opening link in this video.
You
can open your account through it. Your
intraday brokerage there, friends, will not be
zero, that is, it will be around zero.
Friends, they charge a minimum, so the
rest will be charged in a way. So,
friends, I hope you
liked my video and it will be
very beneficial for you. With this hope,
I am ending the video,
thank you.